Guide to the Duke Endowment Archives, 1902-2018 and undated, bulk 1925-2006 RL.00332
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Rural Church Division Series (RESTRICTED), 1918-2006 and undated, 152 boxes
  - Building Grant Files Subseries, 1920-2006 and undated
    - Forrest Home Church, Avery County, 1950 (Box RCD 53)
    - Fountain Hill Church, Anson County, 1934-1978 (Box RCD 53)
    - Four Oaks Church, Johnston County, 1987-1991 (Box RCD 53)
    - Francis Asbury Church, Buncombe County, 1941-1965, 1981-1983, 3 folders (Box RCD 54)
    - Francis Cove Church, Haywood County, 1953 (Box RCD 54)
    - Franklin Church, Macon County, 1935-1937 (Box RCD 54)
    - Franklin Heights Church, Surry County, 1945-1966, 1973-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 54)
    - Franklinton Church, Franklin County, 1972, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 54)
    - Franklinville Church, Randolph County, 1927 (Box RCD 54)
    - Fremont Church, Wayne County, 1926-1958 (Box RCD 54)
    - French's Creek Church, Bladen County, 1928-1931 (Box RCD 54)
    - Friendship Church, Alamance County, 1947-1948, 1977-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 54)
    - Friendship Church, Burke County, 1938-1941, 1968-1974, 1983-1985, 3 folders (Box RCD 54)
    - Friendship Church, Cabarrus County, 1925-1926, 1971, 1989-1990, 3 folders (Box RCD 55)
    - Friendship Church, Catawba County, 1932-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 55)
    - Friendship Church, Davidson County, 1971-1975 (Box RCD 55)
    - Friendship Church, Guilford County, 1933-1972, 3 folders (Box RCD 55)
    - Friendship Church, Iredell County, 1944-1961, 1975-1978, 3 folders (Box RCD 55)
    - Friendship Church, Stanly County, 1961-1964 (Box RCD 55)
    - Friendship Church, Watauga County, 1959-1960 (Box RCD 55)
    - Friscoe Church, Dare County, 1936-1938 (Box RCD 55)
    - Frizzelle Memorial Church, Greene County, 1947-1948 (Box RCD 55)
    - Fruitland Church, Henderson County, 1947-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 55)
    - Fuquay Springs Church, Wake County, 1927-1941 (Box RCD 55)
    - Galilee Church, Cleveland County, 1969-1974 (Box RCD 55)
    - Gamewell Church, Caldwell County, 1937-1966, 2 folders (Box RCD 55)
    - Garber Church, Craven County, 1959-1960, 1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 56)
    - Gardner's Church, Cumberland County, 1955-1982 (Box RCD 56)
    - Garland Church, Sampson County, 1951-1955 (Box RCD 56)
    - Garner Church, Wake County, 1940-1943 (Box RCD 56)
    - Garris Chapel, Wayne County, 1952-1956, 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 56)
    - Garysburg Church, Northampton County, 1946-1977 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gatesville Church, Gates County, 1935-1954, 1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 56)
    - Gay's Chapel, Rowan County, 1952 (Box RCD 56)
    - Germantown Church, Stokes County, 1958 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gethsemane Church, Guilford County, 1920-1946 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gibson Church, Scotland County, 1955-1956 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gibson Memorial Church, Nash County, 1954-1956 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gideon Grove Church, Rockingham County, 1958-1974, 2 folders (Box RCD 56)
    - Gilboa Church, Rutherford County, 1925-1931 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gilboa Church, Union County, 1935-1940 (Box RCD 56)
    - Giles Church, Randolph County, 1951-1952 (Box RCD 56)
    - Gilkey Church, Rutherford County, 1970, 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 56)
    - Gillburg Church, Vance County, 1947-1949, 1971-1972, 1981, 3 folders (Box RCD 56)
    - Glen Alpine Church, Burke County, 1945-1946 (Box RCD 56)
    - Glen Raven Church, Alamance County, undated (Box RCD 56)
    - Glencoe Church, Rockingham County, 1958-1964, 1977-1983, 4 folders (Box RCD 57)
    - Glenville Church, Jackson County, 1925-1926 (Box RCD 57)
    - Glenwood Church, Guilford County, 1927 (Box RCD 57)
    - Glenwood Church, McDowell County, 1940-1948 (Box RCD 57)
    - Glenwood Church, Richmond County, 1945-1958 (Box RCD 57)
    - Golden Valley Church, Nash County, 1955-1956 (Box RCD 57)
    - Goldston Church, Chatham County, 1952-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 57)
    - Good Hope Church, Davidson County, 1921-1979, 2 folders (Box RCD 57)
    - Goshen Church, Sampson County, 1953-1969 (Box RCD 57)
    - Grace Chapel, Caldwell County, 1972-1977, 1988-1991 (Box RCD 57)
    - Grace Church, Anson County, 1959-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 57)
    - Grace Church, Buncombe County, 1954 (Box RCD 57)
    - Grace Church, Dare County, 1965-1967 (Box RCD 57)
    - Grace Church, Pasquotank County, 1956-1958 (Box RCD 57)
    - Grace Church, Randolph County, 1957-1964, 1972, 3 folders (Box RCD 57)
    - Grassy Creek Church, Surry County, 1957-1958, 2 folders (Box RCD 57)
    - Gray Rock Church, Granville County, 1952 (Box RCD 58)
    - Gray's Chapel, Randolph County, 1939-1943, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 58)
    - Green Hill Church, Caldwell County, 1987-1988 (Box RCD 58)
    - Green Lake Church, Richmond County, 1957-1959 (Box RCD 58)
    - Green Memorial Church, Buncombe County, 1962-1963 (Box RCD 58)
    - Green Valley Church, Ashe County, 1951 (Box RCD 58)
    - Greer's Chapel, Davidson County, 1976-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 58)
    - Grifton Church, Pitt County, 1927-1960 (Box RCD 58)
    - Grimesland Church, Pitt County, 1920-1931 (Box RCD 58)
    - Groce Church, Buncombe County, 1954 (Box RCD 58)
    - Groomtown Church, Guilford County, 1953-1962, 1974, 3 folders (Box RCD 58)
    - Grove Hill Church, Granville County, 1984-1985 (Box RCD 58)
    - Halifax Church, Halifax County, 1948-1950 (Box RCD 58)
    - Halls Church, Sampson County, 1962-1963, 1973-1976, 2 folders (Box RCD 58)
    - Hall's Creek Church, Pasquotank County, 1955-1979 (Box RCD 58)
    - Hallsboro Church, Columbus County, 1930-1964 (Box RCD 58)
    - Hamilton Church, Martin County, 1946-1956 (Box RCD 58)
    - Hampstead Church, Pender County, 1929-1930 (Box RCD 58)
    - Hanes-Clemmons Church, Forsyth County, 1925-1927 (Box RCD 58)
    - Hanes Grove Church, Yadkin County, 1940-1942 (Box RCD 58)
    - Hanna Chapel, Anson County, 1962-1968, 2 folders (Box RCD 58)
    - Hardison Church, Davie County, 1955-1967 (Box RCD 58)
    - Harker's Island Church, Carteret County, 1953, 1975-1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 58)
    - Harlowe Church, Carteret County, 1933-1968, 2 folders (Box RCD 59)
    - Harmony Church, Iredell County, 1980-1988, 2 folders (Box RCD 59)
    - Harper's Chapel, Caldwell County, 1940-1944 (Box RCD 59)
    - Harrellsville Church, Hertford County, 1935-1950 (Box RCD 59)
    - Harrisburg Church, Cabarrus County, 1962-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 59)
    - Harrison Church, Mecklenburg County, 1933-1956, 1971-1973, 1984-1986, 3 folders (Box RCD 59)
    - Hatteras Church, Dare County, 1925-1956, 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 59)
    - Hatteras Church, DareCounty, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 149)
    - Haw River Church, Alamance County, 1944-1951 (Box RCD 59)
    - Hawkins' Chapel, Halifax County, 1941-1944, 1975-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 59)
    - Hayes Chapel, Rockingham County, 1982-1985 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hayesville Church, Clay County, 1935-1961, 1973-1974, 3 folders (Box RCD 60)
    - Haywood Memorial Church, Haywood County, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Alamance County, 1967-1971 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Beaufort County, undated (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Currituck County, 1937 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Lincoln County, 1985-1986 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Richmond County, 1930-1933 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Union County, 1986-1988 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hebron Church, Washington County, 1945-1950 (Box RCD 60)
    - Helena Church, Person County, 1922-1954, 1980-1984, 1989-1991, 3 folders (Box RCD 60)
    - Henson's Chapel, Watauga County, 1925-1928 (Box RCD 60)
    - Hermon Church, Vance County, 1974-1975 (Box RCD 61)
    - Hiatt Memorial Church, Forsyth County, 1970 (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Grove Church, Guilford County, 1960-1976, 2 folders (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Grove Church, Lenoir County, 1945-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Grove Church, Mecklenburg County, 1927-1977 (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Grove Church, Rockingham County, 1930-1937, 1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Knoll Church, Macon County, 1954 (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Mountain Church, Chatham County, 1960-1961 (Box RCD 61)
    - Hickory Ridge Church, Forsyth County, 1951-1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 61)
    - Hiddenite Church, Alexander County, 1947-1958 (Box RCD 61)
    - Higgins Memorial Church, Yancey County, 1958-1974, 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box RCD 61)
    - High Falls Church, Moore County, 1959-1979 (Box RCD 61)
    - High Shoals Church, Gaston County, 1950-1951 (Box RCD 61)
    - Highlands Church, Macon County, 1950-1956 (Box RCD 61)
    - Hildebran Church, Burke County, 1949-1965, 1973-1987, 3 folders (Box RCD 61)
    - Hildebran Church, Burke County, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 149)
    - Hill's Chapel, Lincoln County, 1921-1950, 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 62)
    - Hillsboro Church, Orange County, 1941-1944 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hinton's Chapel, Lincoln County, 1986-1989 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hobgood Church, Halifax County, 1952-1955, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box RCD 62)
    - Hobucken Church, Pamlico County, 1933-1950 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hodgin Memorial Church, Rockingham County, 1949-1951 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hoey Memorial Church, Cleveland County, 1985 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hoffman Church, Richmond County, 1939-1950 (Box RCD 62)
    - Holden Memorial Church, Johnston County, 1926-1929 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hollands Church, Wake County, 1974-1981 (Box RCD 62)
    - Holly Springs Church, Martin County, 1928-1931 (Box RCD 62)
    - Holly Springs Church, Wake County, 1927-1928 (Box RCD 62)
    - Homestead Church, Mecklenburg County, 1956-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 62)
    - Hookerton Church, Greene County, 1939-1948 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hope Church, Chatham County, 1944-1949 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hope Mills Church, Cumberland County, 1960-1969 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hopewell Church, Anson County, 1929-1961 (Box RCD 62)
    - Hopewell Church, Randolph County, 1938-1950 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hopewell Church, Rutherford County, 1939-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 63)
    - Hopewell Church, Sampson County, 1952-1976, 1986-1989, 3 folders (Box RCD 63)
    - Hopewell Church, Watauga County, 1938-1940 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hornes Church, Nash County, 1950-1954 (Box RCD 63)
    - Horse Shoe Church, Henderson County, 1956-1958 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hot Springs Church, Madison County, 1954 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hoyle Memorial Church, Cleveland County, 1989-1991 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hudson Church, Caldwell County, 1941-1943 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hunter's Chapel, Mecklenburg County, 1979-1984 (Box RCD 63)
    - Huntersville Church, Mecklenburg County, 1930-1968, 1985-1987, 2 folders (Box RCD 63)
    - Huntsville Church, Yadkin County, 1926-1928 (Box RCD 63)
    - Hyder Mountain Church, Haywood County, undated (Box RCD 63)
    - Indian Trail Church, Union County, 1928-1943 (Box RCD 63)
    - Institute Church, Lenoir County, 1951, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box RCD 63)
    - Iotla Church, Macon County, 1921-1944 (Box RCD 64)
    - Iron Station Church, Lincoln County, 1940-1958 (Box RCD 64)
    - Ivey Memorial Church, Lincoln County, 1939-1968 (Box RCD 64)
    - Jackson Church, Guilford County, 1971-1975 (Box RCD 64)
    - Jackson Church, Northampton County, 1936-1937 (Box RCD 64)
    - Jacksonville Church, Onslow County, 1894-1941 (Box RCD 64)
    - Jamesville Church, Martin County, 1943-1955 (Box RCD 64)
    - Jamestown Church, Guilford County, 1926-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 64)
    - Jefferson Church, Ashe County, 1934-1959 (Box RCD 64)
    - Jerusalem Church, Warren County, 1934-1944, 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 64)
    - Johns Church, Scotland County, 1936 (Box RCD 64)
    - John's Creek, Jackson County, 1984-1985 (Box RCD 64)
    - Johnson's Chapel, Sampson County, 1939-1941 (Box RCD 64)
    - Johnsontown Church, Davidson County, 1931-1957, 1973-1979, 2 folders (Box RCD 64)
    - Jonas Ridge Church, Burke County, 1964-1965, 1977-1979, 3 folders (Box RCD 64)
    - Jones Chapel, Lee County, 1934-1960 (Box RCD 65)
    - Jones Memorial Church, Iredell County, 1956 (Box RCD 65)
    - Jones Spring Church, Richmond County, 1951 (Box RCD 65)
    - Jonesboro Church, Lee County, 1927-1946 (Box RCD 65)
    - Jordan Memorial Chapel, Randolph County, 1983-1991, 2 folders (Box RCD 65)
    - Julian Church, Guilford County, 1963-1968 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kadesh Church, Cleveland County, 1934-1955 (Box RCD 65)
    - Keener Church, Sampson County, 1943-1944 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kenansville Church, Duplin County, 1935-1958 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kenly Church, Johnston County, 1937-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 65)
    - Kimesville: Mount Pleasant Church, Guilford County, 1977-1986, 2 folders (Box RCD 65)
    - Kings Church, Sampson County, 1933-1934 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kingswood Church, Forsyth County, 1971-1976 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kistler Chapel, Rutherford County, 1946-1949, 1977-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 65)
    - Kittrell Church, Vance County, 1926-1931 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kittrell Church, Gates County, 1930-1935 (Box RCD 65)
    - Kitty Hawk Church, Dare County, 1927-1960, 1975-1976, 1986-1987, 3 folders (Box RCD 66)
    - Knightdale Church, Wake County, 1948-1950 (Box RCD 66)
    - Knox's Chapel, Rowan County, 1930-131 (Box RCD 66)
    - Laboratory Church, Lincoln County, 1967-1973 (Box RCD 66)
    - Lake Waccamaw Church, Columbus County, 1946-1947, 1962-1972, 3 folders (Box RCD 66)
    - Landers Chapel, Gaston County, 1925-1959 (Box RCD 66)
    - Lane's Church, Craven County, 1947-1963, 3 folders (Box RCD 66)
    - Lansing Church, Ashe County, 1934-1944 (Box RCD 66)
    - Laurel Church, Madison County, 1959-1960 (Box RCD 66)
    - Laurel Hill Church, Buncombe County, 1950-1973 (Box RCD 66)
    - Laurel Hill Church, Haywood County, 1931-1932 (Box RCD 66)
    - Laurel Hill Church, Scotland County, 1943-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 66)
    - Lawndale Church, Cleveland County, 1951-1961 (Box RCD 66)
    - Lea's Chapel, Person County, 1952-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 66)
    - Leasburg Church, Caswell County, 1944-1966 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lebanon Church, Columbus County, 1930-1956 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lebanon Church, Lincoln County, 1944-1968 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lebanon Church, Orange County, 1936-1938 (Box RCD 67)
    - Ledbetter's Church, Richmond County, 1931 (Box RCD 67)
    - Ledfords Chapel, Clay County, 1936-1939 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lee's Chapel, Guilford County, 1927-1976, 3 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Legend Park Church, Randolph County, 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Leicester Church, Buncombe County, 1929-1931 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lemon Springs Church, Lee County, 1926-1965, 3 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Level Cross Church, Randolph County, 1956-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Level Cross Church, Surry County, 1945-1950 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lewisville Church, Forsyth County, 1931-1939, 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Liberty Church, Davie County, 1939-1969, 2 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Liberty Church, Rowan County, 1927-1966 (Box RCD 67)
    - Liberty Church, Watauga County, 1944-1950, 1974-1976, 2 folders (Box RCD 67)
    - Lilesville Church, Anson County, 1926-1958 (Box RCD 67)
    - Lillington Church, Harnett County, 1926-1968, 2 folders (Box RCD 68)
    - Lineberry Church, Davidson County, 1942-1958 (Box RCD 68)
    - Linville Church, Avery County, 1975-1978 (Box RCD 68)
    - Linville Church, Burke County, 1951 (Box RCD 68)
    - Linwood Church, Davidson County, 1928-1929, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 68)
    - Littlejohn Church, Caldwell County, 1976-1982 (Box RCD 68)
    - Little Laurel Church, Ashe County, 1945-1947 (Box RCD 68)
    - Little Sandy Church, Madison County, 1958 (Box RCD 68)
    - Littleton Church, Warren County, 1940-1958 (Box RCD 68)
    - Live Oak Church, Bladen County, 1940-1941 (Box RCD 68)
    - Locust Church, Stanly County, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 68)
    - Locust Hill Church, Caswell County, 1948-1952 (Box RCD 68)
    - Longhurst Church, Person County, 1945-1955 (Box RCD 68)
    - Long's Chapel Church, Haywood County, 1926-1963, 1979-1980, 4 folders (Box RCD 68)
    - Longtown Church, Yadkin County, 1939-1952 (Box RCD 68)
    - Louisa Church, Haywood County, 1958-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 68)
    - Louisa Church, Macon County, 1955-1965 (Box RCD 68)
    - Love's Chapel, Forsyth County, 1949-1969 (Box RCD 68)
    - Love's Chapel, Jackson County, 1920-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 68)
    - Love's Chapel, Stanly County, 1952-1963, 1977-1979, 4 folders (Box RCD 69)
    - Love Joy Church, Montgomery County, 1986-1988 (Box RCD 69)
    - Lowe's Church, Rockingham County, 1936-1951 (Box RCD 69)
    - Lucama Church, Wilson County, 1927 (Box RCD 69)
    - Mabel Church, Watauga County, 1945-1948 (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Davidson County, 1959-1968 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Davidson County, 2000-2004 (Box RCD 149)
    - Macedonia Church, Iredell County, 1964-1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Lincoln County, 1942-1944 (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Montgomery County, 1951 (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Pitt County, 1949-1951 (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Wake County, 1939, 1969-1983, 3 folders (Box RCD 69)
    - Macedonia Church, Warren County, 1927-1935 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Maggie Church, Haywood County, 1949-1951 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Magnolia Church, Duplin County, 1925-1957 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Magnolia Church, Duplin County, 2001-2005 (Box RCD 149)
    - Maiden's Chapel, Macon County, 1949-1950 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Mann's Chapel, Chatham County, 1925 (Box RCD 69)
    - Mann's Harbor Church, Dare County, 1938-1939 (Box RCD 69)
    - Maple Grove Church, Haywood County, 1937-1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 69)
    - Maple GroveChurch, Jones County, 1938-1945 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Maple Grove Church, Surry County, 1955 and undated (Box RCD 69)
    - Maple Springs Church, Forsyth County, 1945-1948, n.d (Box RCD 69)
    - Maple Springs Church, Randolph County, 1927-1959, 1976-1977, and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 70)
    - Maple Springs Church, Wilkes County, 1980-1983 (Box RCD 70)
    - Marcus Church, Montgomery County, 1951 (Box RCD 70)
    - Marrow's Chapel, Vance County, 1986-1987 (Box RCD 70)
    - Mars Hill Church, Madison County, 1972 (Box RCD 70)
    - Marshall Chapel, Clay County, 1949-1950 and undated (Box RCD 70)
    - Marshall Church, Madison County, 1966-1967, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 70)
    - Marshallberg:Trinity Church, Carteret County, 1950 1976-1982, 1985-1986, 3 folders (Box RCD 70)
    - Marshville Church, Union County, 1925-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 71)
    - Martin's Chapel, Yancey County, 1940-1950 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - Marvin Church, Alexander County, 1953 (Box RCD 71)
    - Marvin Church, Cumberland County, 1952-1958, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 71)
    - Marvin Church, Forsyth County, 1928-1952 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - Marvin Church, Lincoln County, 1929-1935, 1984-1986, and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 71)
    - Marvin Church, Union County, 1953-1973 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - Mary's Grove Church, Cleveland County, 1944-1970 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - Mashoes Church, Dare County, 1935-1936 (Box RCD 71)
    - Massey's Chapel, Durham County, 1931 (Box RCD 71)
    - Matthews Church, Mecklenburg County, 1928-1966 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - Matton's Grove Church, Stanley County, 1976-1982 (Box RCD 71)
    - Maxton Church, Robeson County, 1935 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - Maybrook Church, Durham County, 1947-1951 and undated (Box RCD 71)
    - May's Chapel, Catawba County, 1956-1970, 1984-1986, and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 71)
    - Maysville Church, Jones County, 1926, 1966-1973, 1981-1982, 3 folders (Box RCD 71)
    - McBride Church, Camden County, 1950-1967 (Box RCD 72)
    - McGee Church, Sampson County, 1969-1983 (Box RCD 72)
    - McKendree Church, Edgecombe County, 1955-1956, 1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 72)
    - McKendree Church, Iredell County, 1979-1982 (Box RCD 72)
    - McKendree Church, Lincoln County, 1935-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 72)
    - McMannen's Chapel, Durham County, 1927-1955 1965-1973, 2 folders (Box RCD 72)
    - McQueen's Chapel, Lee County, 1977-1981 (Box RCD 72)
    - Memorial Church, Currituck County, 1928-1935 and undated (Box RCD 72)
    - Memorial Church, Macon County, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 72)
    - Meroney Church, Chatham County, 1928-1929 (Box RCD 72)
    - Merrimon Church, Carteret County, 1929 (Box RCD 72)
    - Merritt's Chapel, Chatham County, 1952-1965, 1980-1987 and undated, 4 folders (Box RCD 72)
    - Messiah Church, Lincoln County, 1970, 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box RCD 73)
    - Micro Church, Johnston County, 1944-1957 and undated (Box RCD 73)
    - Middleburg Church, Vance County, 1927-1929 and undated (Box RCD 73)
    - Middlesex Church, Nash County, 1951-1973 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 73)
    - Midway Church, Davidson County, 1962-1967, 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 73)
    - Midway Church, Iredell County, 1955-1959 and undated (Box RCD 73)
    - Midway Church, Onslow County, 1927-1928, 1973,nd., 2 folders (Box RCD 73)
    - Midway Church, Richmond County, 1943-1945 and undated (Box RCD 73)
    - Midway Church, Rockingham County, 1967-1970 (Box RCD 73)
    - Midway Church, Union County, 1957 (Box RCD 73)
    - Milford Hills Church, Rowan County, 1957 (Box RCD 73)
    - Mill Grove Church, Cabarrus County, 1938-1941 (Box RCD 73)
    - Mill Grove Church, Union County, 1969-1971 (Box RCD 73)
    - Millbrook Church, Wake County, 1931-1971 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 73)
    - Miller's Chapel, Bladen County, 1982-1983 (Box RCD 74)
    - Miller's Creek Church, Wilkes County, 1949-1958, 1972-1977, and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 74)
    - Millers Creek Church, Wilkes County, 2001-2005 (Box RCD 149)
    - Mills River Church, Henderson County, 1945-1959, 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 74)
    - Milton Church, Caswell County, 1930-1935 and undated (Box RCD 74)
    - Milton Church, Caswell County, 2002-2004 (Box RCD 149)
    - Mineral Springs Church, Union County, 1943-1964, 1984-1986, and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 74)
    - Mishop Springs Church, Columbus County, 1945-1948 (Box RCD 74)
    - Mispah Church, Rockingham County, 1955 (Box RCD 74)
    - Mitchell's Chapel, Yadkin County, 1953-1980 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 74)
    - Mitchell's Grove Church, Guilford County, 1957-1990 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 74)
    - Mock's Church, Davie County, 1927-1958, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 74)
    - Moncure Church, Chatham County, 1956 (Box RCD 74)
    - Monk Memorial Church, Pitt County, 1949-1950 (Box RCD 74)
    - Montezuma Church, Avery County, 1954 (Box RCD 74)
    - Monticello Church, Iredell County, 1947-1959 (Box RCD 74)
    - Montmorenci Church, Buncombe County, 1928-1965 (Box RCD 74)
    - Moore's Chapel, Mecklenburg County, 1930-1979, 2 folders (Box RCD 75)
    - Moore's Grove Church, Henderson County, 1948-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 75)
    - Moravian Falls Church, Wilkes County, 1929-1927 (Box RCD 75)
    - Morehead Church, Guilford County, 1940-1964, 1970-1974, 4 folders (Box RCD 75)
    - Moriah Church, Guilford County, 1941-1956, 1967-1972, and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 75)
    - Morning Star Church, Haywood County, 1940-1958 and undated (Box RCD 75)
    - Morris Chapel, Forsyth County, 1952-1960, 1977-1983, and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 75)
    - Morris Chapel, Harnett County, 1926-1927, 1976, 2 folders (Box RCD 75)
    - Morrow's Chapel, Iredell County, 1981-1984 (Box RCD 76)
    - Morven Church, Anson County, 1928-1940 and undated (Box RCD 76)
    - Mott's Grove Church, Catawba County, 1982-1983 (Box RCD 76)
    - Mount Ariel Church, Harnett County, 1958-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 76)
    - Mount Bethel Church, Alexander County, 1959-1966 and undated (Box RCD 76)
    - Mount Bethel Church, Alexander County, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 149)